Hello everyone my name is Kirti Choudhary.
I am from a small place in MP.  I joined
SB Network Marketing a few days ago
and I was feeling very unwell.  So
I have a madam named Dimple Dhakad and I am
also her friend.  Ma'am is also very nice.  So
he told me.  I had a
problem with my spine and I also had pain in my knees.
I also have thyroid.   There
is BP, BP, etc.  So I have been
very upset for two years.  I have been
taking medication for two years now.  It has been at least two and a half years since
I have been taking the medicine.  But then I
talked to my ma'am and she
told me about SBZ, so I
came to SBZ company and then they gave me this
Noni Shiro as you can see.  This
is very good.  He advised me to take it saying it would
benefit me.  This is from
our Ace Network Marketing Company.
I am getting great benefits from drinking this.
This is also helping me lose weight.   I had
lumps in my waist, they are also dissolving.   The
fat that was in my body is also dissolving.  Along with that
I also have energy.
I am able to work well all the time.
Otherwise, earlier there was just laziness, laziness,
laziness of laziness.  But now since
I have got this Noni, I am
drinking it very well.
I will tell you how to drink it.  We have to
take it in a glass.
Boiled or plain water I take lukewarm water.
And we take at least 15 ml in it,
I take two caps because it
suits me well.  Modi ji is not just Modi
ji.  He is not a leader of Bharatiya Janata Party.
Modi ji is the Prime Minister of the country.
It has to be forgotten with a spoonful of fiber.  Believe me, the
taste is very good.  I have been getting
benefits ever since I have been drinking it.  So
whoever has spinal cord problem,
fat problem, thyroid problem can
take this Noni.
APJ Abdul Kalam has written a 150 page
book on this Noni syrup.  If you want, you
can watch it on YouTube or by searching on Google.